[
  {
    "quiz_id": 2,
    "student_id": "Alice",
    "attempt": 1,
    "answers": [
      "180\u00b0",
      "36 cm\u00b2",
      "66 cm",
      "Trapezium",
      "60\u00b0"
    ],
    "score": 5,
    "total": 5,
    "feedback": [
      {
        "question": "What is the sum of interior angles of a triangle?",
        "student_answer": "180\u00b0",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A square has side length 6 cm. What is its area?",
        "student_answer": "36 cm\u00b2",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A circle has radius 7 cm. What is its circumference (use  \ud835\udf0b = 22 / 7 \u03c0=22/7)?",
        "student_answer": "66 cm",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Which shape has exactly one pair of parallel sides?",
        "student_answer": "Trapezium",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "In a right triangle, if one angle is 30\u00b0, the other acute angle is:",
        "student_answer": "60\u00b0",
        "is_correct": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "quiz_id": 2,
    "student_id": "Bob",
    "attempt": 1,
    "answers": [
      "90\u00b0",
      "36 cm\u00b2",
      "66 cm",
      "Rectangle",
      "75\u00b0"
    ],
    "score": 2,
    "total": 5,
    "feedback": [
      {
        "question": "What is the sum of interior angles of a triangle?",
        "student_answer": "90\u00b0",
        "is_correct": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A square has side length 6 cm. What is its area?",
        "student_answer": "36 cm\u00b2",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A circle has radius 7 cm. What is its circumference (use  \ud835\udf0b = 22 / 7 \u03c0=22/7)?",
        "student_answer": "66 cm",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Which shape has exactly one pair of parallel sides?",
        "student_answer": "Rectangle",
        "is_correct": false
      },
      {
        "question": "In a right triangle, if one angle is 30\u00b0, the other acute angle is:",
        "student_answer": "75\u00b0",
        "is_correct": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "quiz_id": 2,
    "student_id": "Champak",
    "attempt": 1,
    "answers": [
      "180\u00b0",
      "18 cm\u00b2",
      "66 cm",
      "Square",
      "50\u00b0"
    ],
    "score": 2,
    "total": 5,
    "feedback": [
      {
        "question": "What is the sum of interior angles of a triangle?",
        "student_answer": "180\u00b0",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A square has side length 6 cm. What is its area?",
        "student_answer": "18 cm\u00b2",
        "is_correct": false
      },
      {
        "question": "A circle has radius 7 cm. What is its circumference (use  \ud835\udf0b = 22 / 7 \u03c0=22/7)?",
        "student_answer": "66 cm",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Which shape has exactly one pair of parallel sides?",
        "student_answer": "Square",
        "is_correct": false
      },
      {
        "question": "In a right triangle, if one angle is 30\u00b0, the other acute angle is:",
        "student_answer": "50\u00b0",
        "is_correct": false
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "quiz_id": 2,
    "student_id": "John",
    "attempt": 1,
    "answers": [
      "180\u00b0",
      "36 cm\u00b2",
      "66 cm",
      "Trapezium",
      "60\u00b0"
    ],
    "score": 5,
    "total": 5,
    "feedback": [
      {
        "question": "What is the sum of interior angles of a triangle?",
        "student_answer": "180\u00b0",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A square has side length 6 cm. What is its area?",
        "student_answer": "36 cm\u00b2",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "A circle has radius 7 cm. What is its circumference (use  \ud835\udf0b = 22 / 7 \u03c0=22/7)?",
        "student_answer": "66 cm",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "Which shape has exactly one pair of parallel sides?",
        "student_answer": "Trapezium",
        "is_correct": true
      },
      {
        "question": "In a right triangle, if one angle is 30\u00b0, the other acute angle is:",
        "student_answer": "60\u00b0",
        "is_correct": true
      }
    ]
  }
]